dotnetcurry.com 2010-11-21

# .NET Curry - Privacy Policy

**Dotnetcurry.com website privacy policy (version 3.0)**

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. ****

**(1)        What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

[(a)    information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views;]

[(b)    information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services (including [ _Name and Email Address_ ]);]

[(c)     information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including [ _Profile details_ ]);]

[(d)    information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters (including [ _details related to the subscriptions_ ]);]

[(e)    any other information that you choose to send to us; and]

[(f)     _Any downloads, service subscriptions etc._ ]

**(2)        Cookies**

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.  (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.)  This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites [, including this one].]

[We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website.  Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers.  The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website.  Google will store this information.  Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.]

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

[(a)    administer the website;]

[(b)    improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;]

[(c)     enable your use of the services available on the website;]

[(d)    send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;]

[(e)    send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;]

[(f)     send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;]

[(g)    send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;]

[(h)    send to you [our newsletter and other] marketing communications (relating to our business [or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties] which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications to be sent by emailing us at [ _administrator@dotnetcurry.com_ ]);]

[(i)     provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;]

[(j)     deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and]

[(k)    _OTHER USES necessary to make the website better_.]

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you: 

(a)      to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b)      in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c)      in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and 

[(d)    to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.]

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

**[(5)      International data transfers**

[Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.]

[If you are in the European Union, information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including [the United States], [Japan], [ _OTHER COUNTRIES_ ]) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Union. You expressly agree to such transfers.]]

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

[We will store all the personal information you provide on servers provided by our webhosting provider.] 

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

[You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.]

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

[We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.] 

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you.  Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee not exceeding $5 or through the consent of the administrator, free of cost.

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email (to administrator@dotnetcurry.com) at any time.  (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

**(10)      Updating information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to [ _administrator@dotnetcurry.com_ ].

This privacy policy is based on a template

created and distributed by [www.website-law.co.uk](http://www.website-law.co.uk/).
